hi and welcome back to my channel I'm
Andrea dudic realtor and your guide to
all things real estate here in Central
Texas now while I normally do things
like give you community tours home tours
and Market updates I'll be doing things
a little bit different today as I take
you on a tour of my top three favorite
self-care spots here in the temple
Belton area our first stop is Beautiful
salon right on Main Street in belon
Texas we're going to interview my hair
stylist Ali I absolutely love her and
I've been going to her for over 5 years
now I think you'll love her too let's
get
[Music]
started so I'm here with Ali Beck um she
has been my hair stylist for over five
years now the best five years of my life
best five years of my life she actually
did my wedding which is a service that
beautiful Salon offers and they were
fantastic so they came out and did my
hair and my bridal party so that was
really awesome and um coming from Vegas
I'm a little bit of a stickler when it
comes to hair care but Allie stuck with
me so um going to ask you some questions
Ally why don't you tell everyone a
little bit about yourself hi I have been
at this uh salon for over 10 years now
and I always joke that it's my on this
relationship but um I love it here we um
love our community and we love our
downtown belon area we donate um a
percentage of our service sales and
retail sales um our profit to Casa which
is just down the road from us and then
we also love to um give back on
Valentine's Day we went to our um Loa H
shelter called K my she and we got to
get them ready for prom so it was so fun
so they're very involved in the
community which I absolutely love and
then um so they're right here on Main
Street in belon so the location is
fantastic they're actually right next
door to woodh house Day Spa which is the
second spot I'll be taking you to um so
Ally what aside from that is there
anything else that you think really make
the salon special and unique to the
Belton area I think our love for our
guests truly shines um especially like
especially Andrea because she's been
here for so long she'll walk in and
everyone knows who she is everyone says
Hi um she's chatting with my co-workers
clients and it really is just like a
family little k i here what are some of
the top services that fun Beautiful
Salon offers so we love Bridal for sure
and we have a whole AC Bridal team and a
full Bridal coordinator um we do cutting
coloring we do the whole family so we do
from infant to um all the grandparents
and men's puts and we offer extensions
we offer smoothing treatments and we do
sell L tanum love it okay and then just
for curiosity purposes what are some
current trends that you see happening in
hairstyle right now so a lot of the
trends right now is like healthy hair
for sure we've been doing a lot more
treatments lately and today mine we do a
lot of um we've been doing a lot of cuts
like where they're like I'm just tired
of my Den like I want to get it all off
so I think healthy hair has been the um
the 2025 Shin for sure love it all right
well uh I you can see why I love Ali and
the salon is absolutely fantastic so if
you're looking for your next favorite
forever hair salon here in the area
you'll definitely want to check out
beautiful Salon in belon Texas and of
course Ali Beck my girl till next time
we would love to have you
bye welcome to the Woodhouse Day Spa
here in belon is conveniently located on
Main Street in belton's Historic
downtown right next door to Beautiful
Salon this facility offers signature spa
services like restorative sleep massage
sculpt facials miscellaneous facials
tons of massages manicures pedicures and
waxing you can find their full list of
services on their website Woodhouse
spas.com
actually my favorite service here is
actually a deep tissue massage which
which gets out all the discomforts and
aches and pains of day-to-day life I
absolutely love it that's my go-to when
you walk in after you check in they'll
go ahead and get you back to their
changing room um where all their lockers
are and you lock up your belongings and
head on over to the quiet room I tried
to get some video of this but there were
quite a few people in there so I could
not but you'll just have to take my word
for it that that room is super peaceful
and super quiet so you're in your robe
you're in the quiet room you can drink
tea Mimosa whatever beverage um you've
decided and once you're called on for
your service you go back for your
service the whole experience is truly
spa-like and something I think really
unique and wonderful for this
area you really can't go wrong with any
of their services head on over to book
your next treatment now so for our last
stop of the day we are at restore your
health in Temple Texas I'm with Allison
the owner and restore your health is an
amazing facility here that offers
services like red light therapy IV
Therapy um whole body Wellness
treatments as well as all things
aesthetic and I've been going here for a
couple years now the things that they
offer I think are very diverse and
really new and needed to this area so
I'll go ahead and let Allison introduce
herself and tell us a little bit about
restore your health hi I'm Alison I
started restore your health about 2
years ago I felt that our community
needed more personalized health care and
so we concentrate on whole body Wellness
we give 30 minutes of undivided
attention with one of our amazing nurse
practition
and we customize your treatment from
keeping you healthy inside and outside
and we also off memberships and so it's
an affordable $50 a month gets you all
of your appointments that are needed and
then we have the add-on services like
$99 ID so a couple questions the first
one is what do you feel are your most
popular and most popular Services I
guess what wellness and aesthetic so
Wellness I definitely feel like most of
people come in and it's either because
their traditional um primary care
provider isn't listening to them um and
they're really struggling with like per
menopause
menopause um not being able to lose
weight and you know they're being tired
of being told like it's just a natural
part of aging so I feel like that's on
the wellness side what most people come
in for and then on the aesthetic side
definitely some
talks Botox is is the it right now yes
it is everybody needs some talks okay
got it and then what do you think is the
most okay so those are the most popular
Services um what is your favorite
service or favorite services that you
offer my favorite service is definitely
um treatment so it's a high intensity
ultrasound that gives you skin
tightening so we lose weight and we get
older skin starts sagging we have this
no downtime non-painful procedure that
just helps you just lift everything back
up sounds great I know sounds great and
then I think I was kind of wondering too
I think there's probably a misconception
that this is something only offered to
men or I mean sorry something that's
only offered to women but I think you
probably do see a lot of men I see it
ton of men I do hormone replacement
testosterone replacement um so we take
care of a lot of our First Responders a
lot of our military um so yeah we do um
and we and it's nice to take care of the
men because then once you're a member
with us you can be seen for all services
so then they're coming in for Testo but
then it's like oh well let's see what
this cholesterol is doing and so then we
can kind of take care of them and make
them healthy all together great everyone
needs it exactly everyone needs it well
if you are interested in any services
from restore your health um Alison can
you give phone number and website yes so
you can reach us at
8699 or head over to our website it's
Resto yourhealth tx.com thank you so
much for joining me today and checking
out my three favorite wellness and
self-care spots here in Temple belon
whether you're looking to move now or
down the road hopefully you will find
some comfort and knowing that you're in
great hands whenever you get here if you
would like more information on
relocating to the area you can download
my free relocation guide you can also
head on over to my website don't forget
to subscribe to my channel like this
video and click the Bell notification so
that you can stay up to date on all
things real estate in Central Texas till
next time